So anyway, hello.
(Lesley:)What are you doing?
(Leonard:)Just extending the intimacy.
Hey, do you wanna slip over
to the radiation lab...
(Leonard:)...and share a decontamination shower?
Okay, what exactly do you think's
going on between us?
(Leonard:)I'm not sure, but I think I'm about
to discover how the banana felt.
(Lesley:)Neither of us are neuroscientists, but we
both understand the biochemistry of sex.
(Lesley:)Dopamine in our brains is released
across synapses, causing pleasure.
(Lesley:)Stick electrodes in a rat's brain,
give him an orgasm button.
(Lesley:)He'll push that thing
until he starves to death.
Well, who wouldn't? Heh.
The difference between us and the rat...
...is you can't stick an electrode
in our hypothalamus.
(Lesley:)That's where you come in.
(Leonard:)Yeah, well,
I'm just glad to be a part of it. Heh.